[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "Will you ever get over this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Rob, what was it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "It was a great evening.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Did the stand he took over gay marriage, do you think, get him right back into the Hollywood firmament in one big hit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, I think there was -- there has been a lot of enthusiasm for President Obama before his position on marriage equality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Well, I mean, I would say that it's -- if the other side decides that they're not going to spend any money on the campaign, then I would say that he probably shouldn't go look for places to raise money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "If you're -- if you're putting an overview on his performance so far, how do you think he's done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I think he's done remarkably well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, I don't know what his thoughts about that are, but I knew -- I don't know that if he ever decides to run for elected office, he'd be terrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "I mean, a 3-year-old boy suckling on his mother's breast, it's ridiculous, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "You know, I think it's best to leave these decisions up to the individual mom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.N. Foundation", "Every Child"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Why are you so fixated on people getting vaccinations for their kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, the U.N. Foundation came together with Every Child by Two to start raising awareness and funds for vaccination campaigns in developing countries -- which I do think is, you know, one of the great medical interventions of our time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "I mean, do you feel these are dangerous statements by celebrities when they say that kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "You know, if you look at the data and the science behind these studies, it seems fairly clear that vaccines are very safe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Are you on the same political side as Mr. Clooney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I think probably in most things, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Clooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Yes, will you be voting for Mr. Obama come November?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "You betcha.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Mother's Day"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Finally, Amanda, how are you spending Mother's Day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, on Mother's Day, I will be with my mother and my mother- in-law.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "You -- do you like doing the interviews?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "You've got a 3-year-old boy, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 240, "question": "What was your honest gut reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "My first reaction was that -- that must be like a European cover version of \"TIME.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "(INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I don't think that's actually how she breastfeeds him at three, but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Don't you just feel deeply uncomfortable looking at that picture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Not deeply, because she's so attractive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Doesn't he go to school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "-- you don't get in the business of telling moms what to do, number one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "There has to be limits, doesn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Who draws it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "-- at cover of \"TIME\" how to -- how to look after her kids?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "``", "NN", "''", "WRB", "TO", ":", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Were you pleased?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Yes, very pleased.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "-- that this is going to force the pace or could it actually create more resistance in a certain sense?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I think you -- I think if you -- if you feel this way on the issue for same-sex marriage, you have to applaud the president for his -- for his bravery in coming out with his personal opinion, right, and stay there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "You study theology?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "How close were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I considered it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carson Daly"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "-- but the words Carson Daly and celibacy aren't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "A reasonably naughty boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "ALY: No, I -- listen, I worked hard and, you know, I dropped out of college and I ended up, you know, broke and living in six cities in California and working in music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What's going on in your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I want to say thank you to everybody that voted for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "How attached do you get to creating a bona fide star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Very, very attached.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Life is good for you at the moment, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJR", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "I mean, personally, you've probably, I would imagine, never been happier, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I've never been happier ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "What have you learned about yourself on this crazy show biz roll you've been on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Just how proud I am of myself, really, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What were the values they wanted you to have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "You know the best thing about it, when I was -- I lost my father when I was 5 years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Siri"]}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Can you believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "You asked Siri every day, presumably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What is the next big ambition for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Gosh, you know, I'm -- I don't take anything for granted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Do you have the empire building ambition of someone like Ryan Seacrest, who you've often been compared with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "No, I don't look at it as empire.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Seacrest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "You don't buy into the purity of the Kardashian lifestyle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "That's not the kind of show I would like to produce, personally.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kardashian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What do you think of Britney Spears joining the \"X Factor\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I think -- I'm excited.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Britney Spears"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "But it is a wonderful story, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "First of all, that term Hollywood royalty really, really scares me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "And what should America and Americans be doing, do you think, to restore it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "CC", "NNPS", "VB", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "My gosh, that's a very -- that's a very heady question there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "If I suddenly went, shut down, cry in five minutes, could you do that like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBN", "RP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Under the right circumstances, probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 696, "question": "What do you tell yourself to make yourself cry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Terrible things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Yeah, you can't go there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "You literally think of awful things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "It's so unnatural, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "What do you feel, Tito, about Conrad Murray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "Well, I feel that like we're supposed to have forgiving hearts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tito", "Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "Do you forgive him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "Sure I forgive him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "Do you all feel that way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "You don't, Jermaine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jermaine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "I feel like it's just negligence and not -- it's on his part plus others.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]